<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>/</id>
  <title>Kai CAS</title>
  <subtitle><![CDATA[A list of Kai's CAS activities + profile]]></subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
  <updated>2022-05-22T02:00:00+02:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Kai CAS</name>
    <uri>/</uri>
  </author>
  <entry xml:lang="en">
    <id>/blog/cycling/</id>
    <title>Cycling</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2 id="cycling">Cycling</h2>
<p>Total time: 25 hours</p>
<p>Bicycling all over the city has taught me a lot, and has helped me stay mentally healthy during the IB process. I found bicycling a great way to clear my mind and to just relax. There’s nothing quite like racing through central park, feeling the breeze pick up on me. I also was able to apply bicycling towards other cities that I visited during vacation. For example, within San Francisco I found bicycling a great and healthy way to explore the city. I biked across and nearby the Golden Gate Bridge and witnessed beautiful views. Note: only a small % of rides were recorded with strava.</p>
<img src={https://i.imgur.com/H3Omyde.jpg} alt="Image alt" />
<img src={https://i.imgur.com/VlgNIKp.jpg} alt="Image alt" />
<img src={https://i.imgur.com/183YNXv.jpg} alt="Image alt" />
<img src={https://i.imgur.com/T3BLdaL.jpg} alt="Image alt" />]]>
    </content>
    <link href="/blog/cycling/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
    <published>2022-05-22T02:00:00+02:00</published>
    <updated>2022-05-22T02:00:00+02:00</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry xml:lang="en">
    <id>/blog/cooking/</id>
    <title>Cooking</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2 id="cooking">Cooking</h2>
<p>Total time: 7 hours</p>
<p>Due to Covid-19 and quarantine, I started to eat out less. Rather, convinced by my parents, I took up cooking. I cooked a variety of meals from mac and cheese to fried rice to kale chips. Cooking helped me enjoy food that I wouldn’t have otherwise enjoyed within the pandemic, and it taught me various cooking techniques. I also learned to further appreciate restaurant chefs, as I started to understand the amount of work that went into cooking. Although I didn't always eat healthy, I learned how to cook healthily and to include lots of greens into my meals whenever possible. Overall, I had a wonderful time cooking and I believe I can apply this skill to other parts of my life.  </p>
<img src={https://i.imgur.com/8bbKONx.jpg} alt="Image alt" />
<img src={https://i.imgur.com/TehXIeG.jpg} alt="Image alt" />
<img src={https://i.imgur.com/HtHqKjb.jpg} alt="Image alt" />
<img src={https://i.imgur.com/dzEhgNK.jpg} alt="Image alt" />]]>
    </content>
    <link href="/blog/cooking/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
    <published>2022-05-21T02:00:00+02:00</published>
    <updated>2022-05-21T02:00:00+02:00</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry xml:lang="en">
    <id>/blog/luv-michael/</id>
    <title>Luv Michael Volunteer</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2 id="luv-michael-volunteer">Luv Michael Volunteer</h2>
<p>Total time: 40 hours</p>
<p>Luv Michael is a non-profit organization which employs workers with Autism to create and sell granola. I was very touched by their cause as I have family members that are affected by autism, and they’ve personally expressed to me the limitations it places on them within finding a job. At Luv Michael, I was a fundraising and advertising volunteer. Volunteering for Luv Michael taught me a lot. I expanded my knowledge on autism and how to appropriately talk about autism. Additionally, I felt impassioned and it was great to work for such a wonderful cause.</p>
<img src={https://i.imgur.com/OoqdAkh.png} alt="Image alt" />]]>
    </content>
    <link href="/blog/luv-michael/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
    <published>2022-05-20T02:00:00+02:00</published>
    <updated>2022-05-20T02:00:00+02:00</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry xml:lang="en">
    <id>/blog/relay-for-life-volunteer/</id>
    <title>Relay for Life Volunteer</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2 id="organization-relay-for-life">Organization: Relay for Life</h2>
<p>Total time: 50 hours </p>
<p>Two years ago, I had the wonderful opportunity to join the Relay for Life team, and help their digital efforts. I was assigned towards maintaining and updating the website, and I also volunteered in person to help aid their fundraising efforts. Through the process, I've learned much about Computer Science and developing the front and back end for websites. Additionally, by spreading awareness for the Relay events and recognizing event sponsors, I’ve led our local relay chapter to raise over $100,000 and gain countless sponsors. Through my work, I've also learned to recognize the importance of working with the team to create change. Without their generous contribution of their time for fundraising, none of the change would be possible.</p>]]>
    </content>
    <link href="/blog/relay-for-life-volunteer/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
    <published>2022-05-19T02:00:00+02:00</published>
    <updated>2022-05-19T02:00:00+02:00</updated>
  </entry>
  <entry xml:lang="en">
    <id>/about/</id>
    <title>About</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<blockquote>
<p>A ready to use static blog, powered by <a href="https://cecil.app">Cecil</a>.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2 id="how-to-use">How to use?</h2>
<h3 id="managing-content-with-forestry-https-forestry-io">Managing content with <a href="https://forestry.io">Forestry</a></h3>
<p>If your goal is managing content quickly, and decide later where to deploy to it, use the following button to import the starter blog to Forestry CMS and start editing immediatelly!</p>
<p><a href="https://cecil.app/cms/forestry/import/"><img src="/assets/assets.forestry.io/import-to-forestryK.ae770f039f3fd871643ef15c32987c4e.svg" alt="Import this project into Forestry" loading="lazy" width="142" height="32" /></a></p>
<h3 id="deploy-with-netlify-https-www-netlify-com">Deploy with <a href="https://www.netlify.com">Netlify</a></h3>
<p>Otherwise, if your goal is deploying a new blog quickly, and manage content mannually, use the following button to configure and deploy your new blog on Netlify.</p>
<p><a href="https://app.netlify.com/start/deploy?repository=https://github.com/Cecilapp/the-butler&amp;stack=cms"><img src="/assets/www.netlify.com/img/deploy/button.3ad9ffd81513851911c7c1ccd470b19b.svg" alt="Deploy to Netlify" loading="lazy" width="146" height="32" /></a></p>]]>
    </content>
    <link href="/about/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
    <published>2019-07-09T02:00:00+02:00</published>
    <updated>2019-07-09T02:00:00+02:00</updated>
  </entry>
</feed>
